1upmedia.biz 2012-05-24

# Online Game Advertising - 1upAds.com

1upAds.com (hereby referenced as 1upAds) is owned and operated by Merendi Networks Inc., a corporation based in Nanaimo, British Columbia, Canada. 

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: 

### Personal Information of Advertisers and Publishers

As required during the registration process for Advertisers and Publishers, 1upAds stores certain personally identifiable information in its database such as (but not exclusive of): first and last name, e-mail address, phone number, country of residence, etc.. 

This information is used to help prevent fraud, provide proper contact information, and for accounting purposes. Any personal information is kept confidential within the scope of 1upAds operations. It is not sold or shared with any 3rd-parties unless legal action requires us to release such information to authorities. 

### E-mail Contact

Apart from providing dedicated customer support, basic site functionality notifications such as ad approvals, and/or to announce any major news such as a security breach, the only other e-mails that Advertisers and Publishers may receive from the site are for the "Receive updates and news pertaining to 1upAds.com" and "Receive daily traffic stats by e-mail" features that would have been checked upon initial registration to the site. 

Advertisers and Publishers can easily opt-out of these two features during registration or at any other time by logging into their account and unchecking the appropriate checkboxes. 

Advertiser and Publisher e-mail addresses are not sold, distributed, or shown to any third party company. 

### Traffic Monitoring

As an ad network, 1upAds tracks network traffic as produced by its Publishers and as paid for by its Advertisers. Therefore, information such as (but not limited to): IP addresses, geolocation, number of clicks and impressions, and referring traffic sources are recorded and kept for the proper use of running the site.

The main use of this information is to provide accurate and detailed traffic reporting and targeting, but it also used to prevent and identify fraud. 

### Cookies

As with virtually every website on the Internet, 1upAds implements cookies on its website. These cookies are used to track numerous types of information such as demographic data (what countries people are visiting from) and what keywords people are using to find 1upAds so that we can better improve our website and service. 

The cookies do not contain any sensitive personal data. If you want to disable the use of cookies you may do so through your browser settings. However, major functionality of the site may not work properly with cookies disabled. 

### Blog Comments

1upAds has a blog which is meant to act as a platform to share news and updates pertaining to the site and service. Advertisers and Publishers are able to comment on our blog. 

While we do moderate the comments, 1upAds does not take responsibility for content created or posted by the community. In addition, please note that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and therefore you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. Your 1upAds username will be shown along with your Blog comment as well, should you leave a comment. 

### External Links and Websites

1upAds will occasionally contain links to other websites. While we try to only link to relevant, quality websites, 1upAds is not responsible for the privacy practices, claims, customer support, content, or other behaviour of these websites. 

### Contacting 1upAds

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you may contact us through our Contact Us page. 

### Your Consent and Acceptance

By using our website and services, you consent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree or accept these terms, you need to cease the use of our website and services. 

### Acknowledgement of Terms of Service

In addition to this Privacy Policy, 1upAds also has a comprehensive Terms of Service. It is advised that this page is read, understood, and agreed to as well. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

1upAds may modify or update this Privacy Policy in the future. Any and all changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on this Privacy Policy page. Any revision(s) will be noted by an updated revised date. Therefore, please check this page on occasion for any changes. 

_Created: September 9th, 2011 _
